Just like crying your eyes out,
laughing out loud is also a basic human need.
Delivery!
Leave it at the door.
He Jiahuan! Bro Chao!
Ow, ow, ow! Bro Chao!
You're ignoring my calls, huh?
No, my phone is on silent.
It's always on silent mode.
Didn't you say you had inside info?
I slipped up, man.
Buying those stocks cost me 200,000!
I... I... I lost money too.
You wanna run, huh?
Why... why would I run?
Well...
The money is right inside.
I'll go get it for you.
Okay?
Let go, it hurts.
If you dare run today, I'll kill you.
No way. It's my house, why would I run?
Bro, come inside.
You guys too. Come in, come in, alright?
I...
After him!
I'm done running.
Hold on, hold on.
Wait, wait.
No, listen.
No.
Don't come any closer! I, I...
I'm calling the police right now!
Officer!
There's a criminal gang here
led by Hu Chaochao.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
They're holding clubs.
Hu as in the surname Hu.
Chao as in Superman. Right.
Come on, call the cops.
Yeah.
Let's see if your fraud charge is worse,
or my debt collecting.
No, Bro Chao, you...
Bro Chao, keep this up and I'll jump!
I'll jump!
Jump.
Jump!
No, no, Bro Chao.
No, Bro Chao, Bro Chao, Bro Chao!
Easy now. Go on, jump!
Think jumping gets you out of your debt?
I was wrong, bro! I was wrong!
Let me tell you,
paying your debts is only right.
If you jump, I'll go after your mom.
Hear me? Wait, bro.
Bro Chao, I'll...
I... I'll find someone.
I'll pay you back in a couple days.
Just give me two days.
I don't have that kind of time. Wait.
Wait for you?
Bro, getting a call.
Maybe this is it. The money's here.
Speak. I'm busy here.
He Jiahuan, where are you?
Fang Haowen is going to jump off a building!
Is he dead?
Not dead. He's trending online.
He's jumping right now!
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
Okay.
Listen, if you have the time,
if you have time to make phone calls right now,
why not borrow some money to save your miserable life?
It's been a while now.
I've really wanted to be in a public place
and laugh out loud.
I want to laugh out loud.
If...
If only this were allowed,
how wonderful it would be.
Just like sobbing uncontrollably,
laughing out loud
is also a basic human need.
This is a poem written by Fang Haowen.
I suddenly think he might be talented.
What does his talent have to do with you?
Let's go.
We're going to be rich! Fang Haowen is viral!
I hate myself.
I hate this world.
Do you remember now?
I wasn't trying to die!
I really can't remember.
I drank way too much.
As for your situation,
we are aware of it.
But I really wasn't trying to jump off a building!
As a success author,
you should take my advice.
Not bothering others is a kind of success.
Remember that.
A miserable life is better than a good death.
Please sign here.
Okay.
If you need anything, call the police.
Thanks for your trouble.
Thank you so much.
I'm heading out. Keep on living.
Take care. See you.
Why are you here?
Why are you so hyped up?
And why do you smell like chicken shit?
Shut up. You went viral, you know that?
Crazy viral. Super viral.
What do you mean super...
Why do you have a chicken feather on your head?
Not important.
What are you doing here?
I'm here to take you home.
You're so viral right now,
could you even get home without me?
Oh, right.
Remember, when we go out later,
don't say anything to the netizens.
Try to squeeze out some tears when we exit.
Can you manage to cry?
Show them a state of severe depression.
That's ridiculous.
I don't even have depression.
What's the situation with these netizens?
I what?
That's enough. This is a hospital.
Stop filming.
Mr. Fang is really depressed.
He really needs some privacy.
Step aside.
Fang Haowen
couldn't handle the harsh realities of society,
which triggered his depression.
Old Fang,
can you tell me first next time?
What a great opportunity you missed.
What do you mean?
Let me review it for you.
Right now,
haven't you finished your second book?
I'll help you publish your second book.
Taking advantage of this current traffic,
let's do a livestream selling your book.
How much money can it make?
How much can it... How much...
I didn't expect so many people to care about my...
underwear.
Stop looking at it.
We haven't secured that underwear endorsement yet.
Old Fang,
let me tell you,
things are different for you now.
Don't worry.
Just trust me with that old face of yours.
I'll sell at least 100,000 for you.
Old Fang, don't you look down on...
making money.
I'm a scholar. How many times have I said it?
Aren't you guys annoying?
Just eat your food.
Old Fang,
you've finally written
the second book of your life.
You want to publish it, right?
But nobody will publish it for you.
Nobody will publish it for you, Old Fang.
I've calculated if you pay out of pocket.
Including ISBNs, printing...
It's at least hundreds of thousands.
You don't have a dime in your pocket.
How are you going to publish it?
Old Fang, let me tell you my strategy.
I'll front the money to publish the book.
We'll form a bond.
I'll find a livestream company for you
to Empower you.
Riding on this current heat,
let's Execute this book-selling plan.
Then you can pay me back the publishing money.
You have to... you have to pay me back.
The publishing money.
And then, then here's my plan.
We'll continue marketing.
We'll continue marketing, stimulate the market,
perfect the logic,
package your New persona,
strengthen netizens' recognition of you.
Let's focus on your scholar attributes.
We'll cross-pollinate the categories.
We'll keep livestreaming.
We'll raise the dimension,
refine our audience,
and consolidate your business model.
You'll get rich off your talent.
Together, we'll walk
the path to the peak of life.
I'm so talented.
Old Fang,
can you play any instruments?
Besides reciting poetry,
do you have any other talents?
I don't...
It's fine, we can package you.
You have a chicken feather on your head.
That's not important.
Let me think about it some more.
My mind's been a mess these past two days.
I just fell off a building!
Isn't that the perfect fall into place?
Stop thinking.
In this information age,
if you don't piggyback on this current traffic,
netizens will forget you in a few days.
If you don't sell your books,
you'll have to jump off the building again in a few days.
Do you believe me? I'll... Wake up!
I'm not asleep.
Fang Haowen, I'll lay it out for you right here.
These days, writing non-stop
and publishing books is totally useless!
You have to promote yourself.
Don't be a lost cause.
If you really want to publish a poetry collection,
come find me tomorrow morning.
If you don't want to,
then go jump again.
Driver, I'm going to report you.
Is this even a ride-hailing car?
It smells so bad.
Don't you know...
...it's bad for us passengers' health?
Take it off. What are you doing?
Your face mask is totally dried out. Take it off.
I'm telling you, if you keep this up...
I'm really going to report you.
Why are my old books still on display?
Well, the second book isn't printed yet.
I called the publisher to rush the printing.
We'll do pre-sales first.
Once the new book is out,
we'll replace the posters too.
Got it.
Mr. Fang!
Mr. Fang! Mr. Fang!
This is great, Mr. Fang! Great!
Lei Oulei, CEO of Erma Media.
Hello, hello!
I read your book.
I absolutely love it!
Thank you.
After finishing your book,
I even became successful!
Thank you.
Which, which chapter do you like specifically?
I like every chapter!
Come, come. This way, please.
Our company
is one of the largest livestream platforms in the country.
The highest annual GMV
for a single streamer is 120 million.
Last year, our company
easily generated a turnover
of 1.4 billion.
Last year, we also effortlessly
trained over 600 streamers.
What you see is just the tip of the iceberg.
All six floors.
Mine.
Mr. Fang, what do you think?
Any advice for us?
Mr. Fang, how about going in to give us some pointers?
No.
Let's go. Right this way, Mr. Fang.
Ready, go!
Welcome, Mr. Fang!
Mr. Fang's writing is pure magic!
Mr. Fang brings immense glory to our company!
Alright, Mr. Fang, Mr. Fang!
Come here, come here, come here!
These guys...
are the Xiaoniudi influencer brothers.
One livestream from these two
starts at ten million.
Mr. Fang, you're currently number three in trending.
If we make good use of this,
combined with our operations...
I humbly wish to promote my new book.
Selling books?
Selling books! Selling books is great!
Is Mr. Fang just selling books?
He's selling the path to success!
You're selling the road to wealth!
However many you print,
we can sell!
But there is one very tricky problem.
Which is, however many you print,
it won't be enough for us to sell!
You're exaggerating. You're exaggerating.
But just selling books is far from enough.
The product line is too limited.
Look at that Pick and Choose account.
Do they only sell books? No.
They also sell general merchandise.
Therefore,
while we're helping you run this livestream,
we'll also help you secure some product slots.
Here, press this.
Our expected revenue is about...
Expected revenue is at least three million. In one night!
Who? Me?
Of course.
I can sell
3 million in one night?
You're definitely worth a fortune a night.
These are just estimates.
It could actually be more.
But...
But I'm just a writer.
I'm a writer.
But I...
can't just sit at home forever.
Actually, for our first livestream,
we don't really want to do livestream selling.
It feels a bit too deliberate.
We won't make it deliberate at all.
Trust me.
I'll tell you
how we'll do it.
We'll promote other things first,
like life values or something.
Then we'll get down to business.
Build up the hype.
Relax, we are the professionals.
I mostly understand the rest,
but I've never done a livestream.
I'm afraid I'll be lost for words.
Whether you're lost for words
doesn't matter at all.
All of your scripts,
we will write them all for you.
You just need to read them.
All product introductions
will be handled by our co-host.
By the way, let me introduce
our beautiful co-host,
Alice.
Hello, Mr. Fang.
Nice to meet you.
Our company's products
are very diverse.
They cover various fields.
The number of partner merchants
has already exceeded 50,000.
So things like food,
clothing, and cosmetics,
are all available for you to choose.
Look,
that is Roujie brand lipstick.
That...
That doesn't really suit me, does it?
That's Little Fool brand's
sunflower seeds and dried sweet potatoes.
I'm a poet with depression.
How would I have time for seeds?
Mr. Fang!
I've heard so much about you!
Hello, hello.
I'm a fan of yours, Writer Haowen.
I got all my culture from you.
Mr. Fang, you have courage and brains,
courage and culture.
You dare to curse the world and jump off buildings.
For tomorrow's trending topic,
how to repeat yesterday's story,
the key is you.
Can Mr. Fang's underwear
leave a spot for our
Sandao logo?
Sandao Underwear
is the title sponsor
for this marketing event.
During our livestream,
we need to give Sandao
some exposure space accordingly.
Exposure space for Sandao Underwear
means that you, Mr. Fang,
during the livestream,
will wear our underwear.
I-I-I can wear it.
That works, but... but...
the viewers won't be able to see it!
Mr. Fang,
the viewers are all very curious
when you jumped off the building that day,
about what brand of underwear you were wearing.
This time, show the logo.
Give them a good look.
I... I have to show my underwear on a livestream?
That's... that's a bit too embarrassing.
I really can't accept this.
I'm just a man of letters.
Mr. Fang,
this isn't just any ordinary underwear.
This is premium, breathable underwear.
Smell this, Mr. Fang.
It has a light scent.
Most importantly,
it's quick-drying.
Here.
Downed it.
I... I... I...
Let me smell, let me smell.
Smells amazing.
He really downed it.
Um, um...
Mr. Fang is knocked out by the smell.
Then I'll... I'll go check.
Thanks.
Mr. Fang, where are you going?
Mr. Fang!
Wait, Fang Haowen, what are you doing?
Aren't I here to sell books?
Why do you keep insisting on
making me show my underwear?
Me, standing there in my underwear,
livestreaming for two hours.
Then I might as well not wear underwear at all!
I'll just sell naked!
I'm a writer.
I can't humiliate myself like this!
Hello? Anyone here?
Hello, cleaning service!
I'm coming in if no one's here!
You think you still have face to lose?
Fang Haowen, let me tell you.
Your ass is just like a piece of pork.
It's only worth something with a label on it.
That Jin Furong
fired you from the magazine
and dragged your name through the mud.
Now, not a single publisher
will advance you money.
Understand?
Don't you want to prove your talent?
But I still can't show my underwear.
Fang Haowen!
Hey, you.
If you're not busy recently,
come back and help me run some operations.
"Author Fang Haowen, depressed over his bad writing,
jumps off a building."
This is already number three on the trending list.
Now, all the netizens want to see
just how terrible his writing really is.
It's making this book sell like crazy!
I guess bad publicity is still publicity!
I plan to market this book as his swan song.
Old Fang.
Jin Furong sent this to me.
Isn't it disgusting?
Doesn't it upset you?
But I don't think that's important.
What's important is
that the whole world's impression of you right now
is that your writing is terrible.
Your second book is so well written.
If we don't hurry and publish it
to change everyone's impression of you,
no one will read your future writing, no matter how good.
Sales or your dignity. You choose.
Old Fang. Old-
If I take my clothes off,
can I really sell my new book?
Sell out completely?
I'm just afraid you won't print it fast enough.
What should I do next?
Mr. Fang.
Did you wash your hands after using the bathroom?
You shouldn't be livestreaming.
You should have some standards as an actor.
Alright, alright, alright.
I know what you're gonna say.
I'm just an actor.
What? Are you gonna call me...
a D-lister? You're an E-lister.
You're an F-lister!
At least I get acting gigs.
Understand? What have you done?
I wrote two books!
Where are they? Come on, let me ask you.
I have over 100,000 people in my stream right now.
I have 20,000 people in my stream.
20,000 people in my stream!
If you weren't jumping off a building,
I'm telling you,
you wouldn't even have two people.
Don't you just want a few Big Rockets?
Just be a good boy and call me "Big Bro,"
and I'll send them to you.
Believe it or not?
You dare utter such wild words!
In that case,
alright, alright.
Tomorrow at noon,
come to my livestream.
I'll see you on the bridge.
No, bros,
look at this guy's attitude.
So-called intellectuals.
A few words and I made him rage-quit.
Great. Mr. Fang. Great job, Mr. Fang.
Is... is it off?
We're done.
It's off, right? Everything's off?
It's off. You can move now.
Man, did he really get mad just now?
Is my face red?
You did pretty well.
I'm fine. It's okay.
Thank you. Thank you. Thanks.
Thanks for your hard work, everyone. Thanks.
Let's... let's... let's go.
Let's look around some more.
On the right.
Actually, actually, I think
there must be
a certain trick to it.
Right. Very, very professional.
Mr. Fang.
Hello, hello, hello.
Hello, Mr. Fang.
Um, I'm really sorry.
I didn't scare you just now, did I?
No, no, no.
I thought it was really, really good.
That provocative energy
was just right.
I totally bought it.
You bought it?
Well, Mr. Fang, here's the thing.
The next time we stream,
you have to yell at me!
If you don't yell at me,
the fans won't get mad,
and they won't send me gifts.
We really didn't know. We'll yell at you next time, next time.
Okay, okay, okay.
It's a pity you're not acting with those skills.
Right?
You should act more.
I really love watching your shows.
Really? Which one is your favorite?
I love every single one of them.
Alright!
How did our livestream do?
Congratulations, everyone.
The hashtag for Mr. Fang's first livestream
made it to the top ten trending topics!
Good, good. That's great! Great!
Come on, let's raise a glass
to witness this milestone today.
Mr. Fang, today's livestream
had over 500,000 views,
and over 100,000 live viewers.
Great, great.
This is great.
And we only did soft promos this time,
without linking the shopping cart.
Next time, I'll push traffic directly to you.
A million in cash!
Okay!
What's more, Mr. Fang...
The director of *Let's Go*
tailor-made a script just for you.
*Farewell Rehearsal*.
Mr. Fang, look.
It pays tribute to your favorite author,
Haruki Muraclimber.
Why make it so...
It's Murakami.
That's not important.
Making money is what's important.
Right.
Are you done changing?
All done.
Mr. Fang.
Then our "Rehearsing Goodbye" is about to begin.
Alice.
You know about livestreams.
Hurry up and explain the flow to Mr. Fang.
Okay.
Mr. Fang,
thanks for your hard work.
Not at all, not at all.
Hurry up.
Mr. Fang.
Hello, hello.
That time with the Fangdan Guy,
your livestream teaser...
was exceptionally good.
Yes, the online response was very enthusiastic.
For this time,
we're cashing in on the crisis.
Cashing in on the crisis?
Right. The plan from the planning team
is
based on you being so insulted by the Fangdan Guy
that you want to jump off a building and commit suicide.
Using your mental breakdown as the foundation,
we've designed a scenario for you.
You don't want me to really commit suicide, do you?
Of course it's fake.
This time, we're doing a
"no suicide, just livestream selling."
Understood, understood.
Come, Mr. Fang,
let me put a mic on you.
Okay.
Have you read it?
Read what?
The script.
I read it, I read it.
Good that you read it.
Mr. Fang,
Ms. Alice, come, let's talk in the car.
Get in, get in.
Let's talk in the car.
Mr. Fang,
this time around,
After you, after you.
we won't put up the shopping link
and we won't sell anything.
It's soft marketing.
The main goal is to establish this persona,
from wanting to commit suicide to finding life's meaning,
and thus living on bravely.
The plot of this story
goes something like this.
Let me explain it to you.
Okay, okay.
How does it go?
You can't stand the insults from the Fangdan Guy,
you suffer from severe depression,
and you seriously consider suicide.
You come to the bridge
and plan to jump off.
At this moment,
we need to show a bit of
our sponsors' products
to increase their exposure, okay?
At the same time,
Just as you're about to leave
your miserable life behind,
you suddenly see someone jumping off a bridge too.
So you jump down
and save him.
It turns out
he's a fan of yours.
He's read your book.
He says your book healed him.
At this point, there'll be
a barrage of comments on the screen.
And then, encouraged by the comments,
the two of you bravely go on living.
Please get out.
By the way, Mr. Fang, don't worry.
The water is very shallow.
It's only about this deep.
Just jump down fearlessly, okay?
Okay.
A word in private.
Um, when do we show the underwear?
When Mr. Fang comes out of the water,
his pants will definitely be wet.
That's when he takes them off,
and the underwear naturally gets exposed.
That's good. That's good.
Okay, he takes them off, the wind blows,
and the underwear dries instantly.
Instantly.
You can even smell a faint fragrance.
A faint fragrance.
Great idea.
This is really good. Um,
that actor over there, come here.
Hello, Mr. Fang.
Here he comes.
This actor is...
Oh my god.
Yes, he's the one jumping off the bridge.
Let's run through the lines.
Hello, Mr. Fang.
I'm a fan of yours.
Really?
Fake.
Aren't we running through the lines?
That was all for nothing.
Let's try again.
Stick to your lines.
And follow my emotional cues.
Okay? Come on.
Hello, Mr. Fang.
I'm a fan of yours.
If only that were true.
Mr. Fang.
Hello, hello.
Did you save me?
I did.
I'm Fang Haowen.
All this time,
I've been relying on your books
to keep me going until today.
However,
my failing business
and relationship struggles have crushed me.
You, my pillar of support,
were about to end your own life too.
It made me completely lose hope in life.
Today,
I was supposed to wear my favorite brand,
Falling Cat,
and end my life.
But God let me meet you,
and you saved me.
I have mixed feelings right now.
I hope you can point me in the right direction.
That's great.
Professional.
Professionally trained.
Yes. Great. So good.
Truly wonderful.
My turn.
Yes, yes, yes.
I thought I was the most
miserable person in the world.
Little did I know, everyone else suffers even more.
I began to doubt the meaning of life.
Until I met you, who wanted to end it all,
and who is also a fan of mine.
You helped me rediscover my mission.
I want to use my second book
to save people like you
who are stuck in the depths of despair.
A-
lice.
Alice.
Your name is too hard to say.
C-can I call you Xiao Ai?
Sure.
You can call me anything.
Hello, Xiao Ai.
I'm here.
Alice.
I, I, I...
Based on our
"Farewell Rehearsal"
script,
I wrote down some
of my own feelings and thoughts.
Do you think I could
share them? Say them out loud?
Say them out loud.
Go ahead.
Sure, sure. Then I'll...
I j-just wrote a couple of lines.
Okay, okay.
It goes like this.
My first book
is the beginning of your path to success.
My second book
is to help you find the gene of success.
Great.
Okay.
As for my second book,
it's not about how to succeed,
but rather, when your life
reaches its hardest, most painful point,
and you can't go on anymore,
it's about how to face it calmly,
a book about surpassing yourself.
Actually, this book has already
been listed in the livestream shopping cart.
Yes, but no one is watching right now.
I'm in pain, agonized,
and also very sad.
Mr. Fang, don't be sad.
I'll place an order right now.
To find my own genes.
Mr. Fang,
your underwear seems dry.
It really is quick-drying.
Refreshing and breathable.
Right, right.
Most importantly, it also has this
faint fragrance.
Yes.
A faint fragrance.
That's great, Mr. Fang.
How about you pull your pants up first?
That was great, Mr. Fang.
But it was just a little bit too tedious.
How about we cut a couple of lines?
Sure, sure.
Okay.
Then, Mr. Fang,
when the time comes,
we'll walk over to that mark.
Then you give the book to the actor from just now.
During the livestream,
the actor will thank you.
Remember,
we need to show this livestream...
wait, the cover of this book,
to the audience.
And we must urge the audience to cherish life.
At the same time, make sure to emphasize
to click the reserve button in the top left corner,
and reserve the next livestream selling, okay?
Okay, alright, alright.
Understood, understood. Okay.
Pretty much understood.
This is
the boss of Jile Razors.
Mr. Fang, I'm Gangster Ba.
I play with blades.
Hello, hello.
Just kidding.
And this is Jianhua.
Hello, Mr. Fang.
Hello, hello.
I'm Scholar Hua.
Life is unpredictable,
but I have a sausage.
A Harbin red sausage.
A pun.
Just a little joke, a little joke.
Don't forget the products in the middle.
What about the product order?
They all must be shown.
The shaver must be shown for at least ten seconds.
Otherwise, the client won't pay the slot fee.
Got it?
What slot?
Slot. Slot means money.
Scamming for money?
What scamming?
We just want to make money.
Shaver on the left, sausage on the right.
Put it here. Okay.
Okay.
Mr. Fang.
Mr. Fang. Here, here, here.
Okay, here, here. The mark is here.
Okay, the mark is here.
Stand here, right?
You'll stand right here later.
Okay.
Mr. Fang, for this livestream,
the whole company has given it our all.
You can promote your book however you like.
But I have two requirements.
First, the products must be shown.
Second,
the livestream cannot stop.
The livestream cannot stop.
Otherwise, my 1 million on traffic goes down the drain.
Don't worry, Mr. Lei. Don't worry.
Mr. Fang, 1 million!
Make sure nothing stops!
Okay.
Are you ready?
Come on, come on.
We're good to go, right?
Right, right. Wait, wait.
My... my...
Come here. My second book...
Book, book, book.
Right, right, okay.
Mr. Fang,
if you can't remember the lines,
there's a teleprompter over there.
you just need to glance at it.
I don't think a teleprompter
is necessary, right?
That's great.
Mr. Fang is a professional, right?
Right.
Okay, Director.
Okay, get ready.
Ten, nine, eight...
1,000 viewers!
5,000 viewers!
Five...
10,000 viewers!
50,000 viewers!
100,000 viewers!
Go!
I am Fang Haowen.
Hao as in vast, wen as in literature.
I was but a drop of water in the vast sea of literature.
Just a mere scholar.
I once wrote a book, "What is Success".
The book sold quite well back then.
My follower count on the hot list also went up a lot.
I felt like I had succeeded.
I underestimated life.
Life started to trample on me.
Time wasted me away.
My lover abandoned me.
My friends despised me.
Even my fans, you all...
began to gradually forget me.
*I "Have No" Talent*
This book is about to go on sale,
yet no one cares.
Yesterday, an actor mocked me in a livestream,
questioning if I really wanted to die.
I was thinking,
if it allows my second book
to help more people,
I think
I can take this step.
I, Fang Haowen,
came into this world clean,
and I'll leave it clean.
I gotta say.
The Jile razor really is quite smooth.
Shave! Why did you put it away?
Before leaving, have a bite.
The last taste of home.
Boss, what did we agree on?
You don't take me, Bro Eight, seriously, do you?
B-b-b-Bro Eight!
You won't stop until you see blood, huh?
Harbin red sausage.
Still the taste of childhood.
The meat content is still so high.
Fang Haowen!
No pay if you don't shave for ten seconds! Hurry!
The razor! They pay more for the red sausage!
Why does the sausage pay less than the razor?
Jile razor.
Watch, give me the watch.
Come, come, come.
Eat the sausage! Eat! Eat the sausage!
The meat content is still...
Is that right? Are the lines right?
Why did you put it away?
Eat the sausage! Eat, eat, eat!
Harbin red sausage.
They won't pay! Keep shaving!
Doesn't hurt the skin at all.
Look, together! Let's do it together! Together!
Jile red sausage!
You think I, Ah Ba, am a pushover?
Harbin red sausage.
He pulled it out.
Know anything about playing with knives?
Bro Eight! Bro Eight!
Eat the sausage! Eat, eat! Eat the sausage!
Eat the sausage! Eat the sausage!
Razor.
Both of these are great.
Together.
Do a combo platter.
Mr. Fang, I...
Mr. Fang!
Mr. Fang, don't jump!
Don't jump!
Mr. Fang!
Who are you?
Mr. Fang, you can't die!
You're... you're... Mr. Fang, calm down!
Who are you? You... who are you?!
Fang Haowen, keep shaving!
It hasn't been ten seconds yet! Hurry and shave!
Who is this? Keep shaving!
Don't stop! Shave!
You have to keep going! Jile Razor!
You have to keep going!
Skin-friendly!
Mr. Fang, you can't hurt yourself!
I'm cut!
Who is this guy? Can someone drag him away?!
The stream can't stop! It can't stop!
Who cares about him! What about me?!
We absolutely can't stop! You planned this!
Hold on a second!
No, no!
Let go of me!
Mr. Fang!
Changing the script?
I didn't!
Changing the script live on set!
Get someone over here!
Somebody! Somebody! Somebody!
Somebody!
Get someone here!
Okay!
Come on!
What do you take me, Ah Ba, for?!
Camera on Mr. Fang!
Mr. Fang is saving a life! Quick!
What am I supposed to do if he jumps?
Go, go, go! Keep up, keep up!
Thanks for the trouble.
Is the water temperature okay?
I'm fine, I'm fine.
Mr. Fang.
I'm a fan of yours.
I'm not Mr. Fang.
He's Mr. Fang.
Well...
Am I seeing double?
Look at this.
Mr. Fang.
Did you save me?
I saved you.
You two saved me.
Right, yes, he saved you.
I am Fang Haowen.
Mr. Fang Haowen.
I'm a fan of yours.
Mr. Fang, I'm a fan of yours too.
All this time,
your books have been what kept me going.
your books have been what kept me going too.
W-Well, thank you.
Thank you both.
You're welcome.
But my failed business
and relationship troubles have been crushing me.
What happened?
Tell me more about it.
What's going on here?
You guys explain.
No need to elaborate, keep going.
Mr. Fang.
Seeing you, my pillar of support,
also trying to end your own life
has made me completely lose hope in life.
Right.
It's so disappointing.
Mr. Fang, why did you jump into the river?
Tell us more about it.
Let him...
Let... let...
He hasn't finished yet.
Let him finish first.
Today
was supposed to be the day I wore my favorite brand,
Falling Cat,
to end my own life.
But God made me run into you.
You two.
And then you saved me.
I... I... I...
I have very mixed feelings right now.
Can one of you give me some guidance?
I...
In a person's life,
success is only temporary.
Failure is the main theme.
But how we face failure
is what sets people apart.
I always thought
I was the most miserable person in the world.
I didn't expect everyone else to suffer more than me.
You just...
What you just said...
Why does it sound so familiar?
These are all things you taught us.
There's no such line! There's none!
Say it. Just say it. You say it.
Just read it as it is.
Mr. Fang, do you still remember me?
My first book
was the beginning of your journey to success.
Then what about my second book?
It's actually about helping you find the success gene.
You published a second book?
Exactly!
Then where is my second book?
The book!
Where is my second book?
Where's the second book? Give it to him!
This is the second book I wrote.
And this one is...
not about how to succeed.
It's rather about
how, when you encounter life's hardships
and feel you can't go on,
to transcend yourself.
Actually, this book
is already in the livestream's shopping cart,
but nobody is looking at it.
I... I'm in a lot of pain.
I'm also very sad.
It ac-
Mr. Fang!
Don't be in pain!
I'll place an order right now!
No, no. I-I-I...
I should be the one ordering.
I'll order! Where on earth did you come from?
What does it have to do with you?
You say, "Mr. Fang,
then what about your...
what about your underwear?"
Fang Haowen! Take it off!
Take it off! Take it off!
Take it off. Hurry up and take it off.
It's not wet, how can I take it off?
Why do you care so much? Take it off!
Mr. Fang...
I... I'm a little cold.
Cold?
If you're cold, that's easy! Come here.
Mr. Fang!
Why are you taking off your pants?
He... He's cold!
Mr. Fang, you can't take off your pants. I'm cold.
He's cold! Mr. Fang, I'm freezing!
If he's cold, why are YOU taking off your clothes?
Mr. Fang, say your lines!
It's not wet! It's not wet! It's not wet!
He's freezing! He's catching a cold!
I'm really cold.
He'll get pneumonia and everything!
What are you doing?
What are you guys doing?
I'm just passing by.
I came here to play in the water.
Play in the water?
Playing in the water, huh?
Doing it this way works, right?
Doing it like this, huh?
Look, what's going on here?
Alice, those two...
Going live like this, right?
My 10 seconds...
Shanghai Aba...
The Sandao underwear Mr. Fang is wearing...
He's wearing Sandao underwear.
My red sausage is exceptionally good.
It's an old brand.
Harbin.
With a subtle fragrance.
The livestream got banned. Are you happy now?
We were streaming just fine,
why did you have to step into the frame?
If I didn't step in,
how could our Sandao brand get proper exposure?
And why did you go up there?
He agreed to eat one, but ate half and stomped on the rest.
What else could I do but go up and eat it myself?
Who the hell was that guy anyway?
Why did you have to get two people
to play one role?
Who was it?
But our numbers were good.
Mr. Fang, I'm your fan.
Are you done?
A fan? Do you want some duck blood?
No. Who sent you?
Why did no one tell me?
Why... Just why...
Why?
I came here on my own.
Alright, the act is over.
What? Are you done yet?
That's enough.
Mr. Fang, do you remember me?
I'm a big fan of yours!
"What Is Success"
Chapter One, Section One
Success is a full stomach.
Section Two
Success is breathing fresh air.
Section Three
Success is being a little selfish.
"What Is Success"
Preface
We usually divide success into three elements.
Persistence, control, and acceptance.
A true fan.
Mine.
Yours.
I don't want you to die.
Why don't you want him to die?
I've been bullied since I was a kid.
And I didn't have many friends.
It was after reading Mr. Book's fang...
Fang... Mr. Fang's...
reading Mr. Book's fang...
that my life started to change.
The year I was born...
You don't need to go that far back.
Page 19 of "What is Success":
Success must have a beginning and an end.
I have to start from the very beginning.